[{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664179793,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":13778,"timeElapsed":190036},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664188976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":9181,"timeElapsed":199219},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664196222,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":7244,"timeElapsed":206465},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664204108,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":7884,"timeElapsed":214351},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664211322,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":7213,"timeElapsed":221565},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664219206,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":7882,"timeElapsed":229449},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664224133,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":4925,"timeElapsed":234376},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664227872,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3738,"timeElapsed":238115},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664231406,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":3533,"timeElapsed":241649},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664242810,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":10104,"timeElapsed":253052},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664254203,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":11392,"timeElapsed":264446},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664257926,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3722,"timeElapsed":268169},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664263021,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":5093,"timeElapsed":273264},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664272338,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":9316,"timeElapsed":282581},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664276876,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4537,"timeElapsed":287118},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664281422,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4545,"timeElapsed":291665},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664284596,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":3174,"timeElapsed":294839},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664288192,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3594,"timeElapsed":298435},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664296736,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":7137,"timeElapsed":306978},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664299508,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2771,"timeElapsed":309751},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664302263,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2753,"timeElapsed":312506},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664304450,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2185,"timeElapsed":314693},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664306766,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2314,"timeElapsed":317009},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664309669,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2901,"timeElapsed":319912},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664315981,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6310,"timeElapsed":326223},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664321148,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":5165,"timeElapsed":331390},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664324751,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":3602,"timeElapsed":334994},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664334272,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":9519,"timeElapsed":344514},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664342565,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":6875,"timeElapsed":352808},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664344262,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1695,"timeElapsed":354505},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664347298,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3035,"timeElapsed":357541},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664352598,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":5298,"timeElapsed":362841},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664355346,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2746,"timeElapsed":365589},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664358556,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3208,"timeElapsed":368799},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664364539,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":5982,"timeElapsed":374782},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664368017,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":3476,"timeElapsed":378260},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664370452,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":2434,"timeElapsed":380695},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664376889,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":5137,"timeElapsed":387132},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664378853,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1963,"timeElapsed":389096},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664381622,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2768,"timeElapsed":391865},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664383916,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2293,"timeElapsed":394158},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664388439,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4522,"timeElapsed":398682},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664392902,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4461,"timeElapsed":403145},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664395650,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2747,"timeElapsed":405893},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664398246,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2594,"timeElapsed":408489},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664400622,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2374,"timeElapsed":410865},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664407576,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":5758,"timeElapsed":417819},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664410209,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2631,"timeElapsed":420452},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664412721,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2511,"timeElapsed":422964},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664415990,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3267,"timeElapsed":426233},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664419468,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":3476,"timeElapsed":429711},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664422915,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":3445,"timeElapsed":433158},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664427347,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":4430,"timeElapsed":437590},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664429335,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":1987,"timeElapsed":439578},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664433348,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":4012,"timeElapsed":443591},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664440776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":6068,"timeElapsed":451019},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664443595,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2819,"timeElapsed":453838},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664446401,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2804,"timeElapsed":456644},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664448344,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1942,"timeElapsed":458587},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664451658,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":3313,"timeElapsed":461901},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664453700,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2041,"timeElapsed":463943},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664456397,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2696,"timeElapsed":466640},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664460391,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":3992,"timeElapsed":470634},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664462488,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2096,"timeElapsed":472731},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664472288,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":8582,"timeElapsed":482531},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664477417,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5127,"timeElapsed":487660},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664484339,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":6920,"timeElapsed":494582},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664486501,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2162,"timeElapsed":496744},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664488262,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1759,"timeElapsed":498505},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664491428,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3165,"timeElapsed":501671},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664493453,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2024,"timeElapsed":503696},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664496467,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3014,"timeElapsed":506710},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664501445,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":4976,"timeElapsed":511688},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664504845,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3399,"timeElapsed":515088},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664510260,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3998,"timeElapsed":520503},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664513036,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2774,"timeElapsed":523279},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664525281,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":12244,"timeElapsed":535524},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664528344,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3060,"timeElapsed":538587},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664531602,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3256,"timeElapsed":541845},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664533758,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2154,"timeElapsed":544001},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664536202,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2442,"timeElapsed":546445},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664538797,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":2593,"timeElapsed":549040},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664540989,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2190,"timeElapsed":551232},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664546067,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3924,"timeElapsed":556310},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664547552,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1483,"timeElapsed":557795},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664550828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3274,"timeElapsed":561071},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664552655,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":1825,"timeElapsed":562898},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664555780,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3123,"timeElapsed":566023},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664557972,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2191,"timeElapsed":568215},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664561010,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3037,"timeElapsed":571253},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664563199,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":2188,"timeElapsed":573442},{"subjectID":"lk6gs2wm05","prolificID":"66e039e38ef91b78f1737632","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ebe7f4645d4f66091","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664565901,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2700,"timeElapsed":576144}]